{"Questions": { "Question #160 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which method helps to optimize costs of users moving to the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Paying only for what is used", "B. Purchasing hardware before it is needed", "C. Manually provisioning cloud resources", "D. Purchasing for the maximum possible load"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.cloudmanagementinsider.com/ways-to-optimize-aws-cost/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #161 Topic 2":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following is a customer responsibility?", "answers":[ "A. Installing security patches for the Xen and KVM hypervisors", "B. Installing operating system patches for Amazon DynamoDB", "CORRECT:C. Installing operating system security patches for Amazon EC2 database instances", "D. Installing operating system security patches for Amazon RDS database instances"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #162 Topic 2":{ "question":"The AWS Cost Management tools give users the ability to do which of the following? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Terminate all AWS resources automatically if budget thresholds are exceeded.", "B. Break down AWS costs by day, service, and linked AWS account.", "CORRECT:C. Create budgets and receive notifications if current of forecasted usage exceeds the budgets.", "CORRECT:D. Switch automatically to Reserved Instances or Spot Instances, whichever is most cost-effective.", "E. Move data stored in Amazon S3 to a more cost-effective storage class."],"explanation": "","discussions": "10"}, "Question #163 Topic 2":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, the security and patching of the guest operating system is the responsibility of:", "answers":[ "A. AWS Support", "CORRECT:B. the customer", "C. AWS Systems Manager", "D. AWS Config"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #164 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service makes it easy to create and manage AWS users and groups, and provide them with secure access to AWS resources at no charge?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Direct Connect", "B. Amazon Connect", "CORRECT:C. AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)", "D. AWS Firewall Manager"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/console_controlling-access.html https://aws.amazon.com/iam/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #165 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides on-demand of AWS security and compliance documentation?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Directory Service", "CORRECT:B. AWS Artifact", "C. AWS Trusted Advisor", "D. Amazon Inspector"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/artifact/#:~:text=AWS%20Artifact%20is%20your%20go,reports%20and%20select%20online%20agreements.","discussions": "1"}, "Question #166 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service can be used to turn text into life-like speech?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Polly", "B. Amazon Transcribe", "C. Amazon Rekognition", "D. Amazon Lex"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/polly/#:~:text=Amazon%20Polly%20is%20a%20service,synthesize%20natural%20sounding%20human%20speech.","discussions": "1"}, "Question #167 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is one of the core principles to follow when designing a highly available application in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Design using a serverless architecture", "CORRECT:B. Assume that all components within an application can fail", "C. Design AWS Auto Scaling into every application", "D. Design all components using open-source code"],"explanation": "","discussions": "1"}, "Question #168 Topic 2":{ "question":"A user needs to generate a report that outlines the status of key security checks in an AWS account. The report must include: ✑ The status of Amazon S3 bucket permissions. ✑ Whether multi-factor authentication is enabled for the AWS account root user. ✑ If any security groups are configured to allow unrestricted access. Where can all this information be found in one location?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon QuickSight dashboard", "B. AWS CloudTrail trails", "CORRECT:C. AWS Trusted Advisor report", "D. IAM credential report"],"explanation": "Reference - https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/#Security","discussions": "1"}, "Question #169 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which Amazon EC2 pricing model should be used to comply with per-core software license requirements?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Dedicated Hosts", "B. On-Demand Instances", "C. Spot Instances", "D. Reserved Instances"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/dedicated-hosts/pricing/","discussions": "0"}, "Question #170 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the AWS global infrastructure is used to cache copies of content for faster delivery to users across the globe?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Regions", "B. Availability Zones", "CORRECT:C. Edge locations", "D. Data centers"],"explanation": "When your web traffic is geo-dispersed, it's not always feasible and certainly not cost effective to replicate your entire infrastructure across the globe. A CDN provides you the ability to utilize its global network of edge locations to deliver a cached copy of web content such as videos, webpages, images and so on to your customers. To reduce response time, the CDN utilizes the nearest edge location to the customer or originating request location in order to reduce the response time. Throughput is dramatically increased given that the web assets are delivered from cache. For dynamic data, many CDNs can be configured to retrieve data from the origin servers. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/caching/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #171 Topic 2":{ "question":"Using AWS Config to record, audit, and evaluate changes to AWS resources to enable traceability is an example of which AWS Well-Architected Framework pillar?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Security", "B. Operational excellence", "C. Performance efficiency", "D. Cost optimization"],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/architecture/AWS_Well-Architected_Framework.pdf (12)","discussions": "1"}, "Question #172 Topic 2":{ "question":"A user needs to quickly deploy a non-relational database on AWS. The user does not want to manage the underlying hardware or the database software. Which AWS service can be used to accomplish this?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon RDS", "CORRECT:B. Amazon DynamoDB", "C. Amazon Aurora", "D. Amazon Redshift"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/amazondynamodb/latest/developerguide/SQLtoNoSQL.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #173 Topic 2":{ "question":"A Cloud Practitioner is developing a disaster recovery plan and intends to replicate data between multiple geographic areas. Which of the following meets these requirements?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Accounts", "CORRECT:B. AWS Regions", "C. Availability Zones", "D. Edge locations"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.botmetric.com/blog/having-a-disaster-recovery-plan-is-pivotal-the-dos-and-donts-on-aws-cloud/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #174 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which features and benefits does the AWS Organizations service provide? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Establishing real-time communications between members of an internal team", "B. Facilitating the use of NoSQL databases", "C. Providing automated security checks", "CORRECT:D. Implementing consolidated billing", "CORRECT:E. Enforcing the governance of AWS accounts"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #175 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service is used to automate configuration management using Chef and Puppet?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Config", "CORRECT:B. AWS OpsWorks", "C. AWS CloudFormation", "D. AWS Systems Manager"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/opsworks/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #176 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which tool is best suited for combining the billing of AWS accounts that were previously independent from one another?", "answers":[ "A. Detailed billing report", "CORRECT:B. Consolidated billing", "C. AWS Cost and Usage report", "D. Cost allocation report"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #177 Topic 2":{ "question":"The AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator is used to:", "answers":[ "A. receive reports that break down AWS Cloud compute costs by duration, resource, or tags", "CORRECT:B. estimate savings when comparing the AWS Cloud to an on-premises environment", "C. estimate a monthly bill for the AWS Cloud resources that will be used", "D. enable billing alerts to monitor actual AWS costs compared to estimated costs"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #178 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services can be used to provide network connectivity between an on-premises network and a VPC? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Route 53", "CORRECT:B. AWS Direct Connect", "C. AWS Data Pipeline", "CORRECT:D. AWS VPN", "E. Amazon Connect"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/directconnect/faqs/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #179 Topic 2":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following are customer responsibilities? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Setting up server-side encryption on an Amazon S3 bucket", "B. Amazon RDS instance patching", "CORRECT:C. Network and firewall configurations", "D. Physical security of data center facilities", "E. Compute capacity availability"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "0"}, "Question #180 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan level that will provide users with access to the AWS Support API?", "answers":[ "A. Developer", "B. Enterprise", "CORRECT:C. Business", "D. Basic"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #181 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company has deployed several relational databases on Amazon EC2 instances. Every month, the database software vendor releases new security patches that need to be applied to the databases. What is the MOST efficient way to apply the security patches?", "answers":[ "A. Connect to each database instance on a monthly basis, and download and apply the necessary security patches from the vendor.", "CORRECT:B. Enable automatic patching for the instances using the Amazon RDS console.", "C. In AWS Config, configure a rule for the instances and the required patch level.", "D. Use AWS Systems Manager to automate database patching according to a schedule."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/rds/faqs/","discussions": "10"}, "Question #182 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company wants to use Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) to deploy a global commercial application. The deployment solution should be built with the highest redundancy and fault tolerance. Based on this situation, the Amazon EC2 instances should be deployed:", "answers":[ "A. in a single Availability Zone in one AWS Region", "B. with multiple Elastic Network Interfaces belonging to different subnets", "CORRECT:C. across multiple Availability Zones in one AWS Region", "D. across multiple Availability Zones in two AWS Regions"],"explanation": "Reference: https://jayendrapatil.com/aws-high-availability-fault-tolerance-architecture-certification/","discussions": "9"}, "Question #183 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company has an application with users in both Australia and Brazil. All the company infrastructure is currently provisioned in the Asia Pacific (Sydney) Region in Australia, and Brazilian users are experiencing high latency. What should the company do to reduce latency?", "answers":[ "A. Implement AWS Direct Connect for users in Brazil", "B. Provision resources in the South America (SÃ£o Paulo) Region in Brazil", "CORRECT:C. Use AWS Transit Gateway to quickly route users from Brazil to the application", "D. Launch additional Amazon EC2 instances in Sydney to handle the demand"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/transit-gateway/","discussions": "6"}, "Question #184 Topic 2":{ "question":"An Amazon EC2 instance runs only when needed yet must remain active for the duration of the process. What is the most appropriate purchasing option?", "answers":[ "A. Dedicated Instances", "B. Spot Instances", "C. On-Demand Instances", "CORRECT:D. Reserved Instances"],"explanation": "Reference: https://jayendrapatil.com/aws-ec2-instance-purchasing-option/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #185 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS dashboard displays relevant and timely information to help users manage events in progress, and provides proactive notifications to help plan for scheduled activities?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Service Health Dashboard", "CORRECT:B. AWS Personal Health Dashboard", "C. AWS Trusted Advisor dashboard", "D. Amazon CloudWatch dashboard"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/personal-health-dashboard/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #186 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS hybrid storage service enables a user's on-premises applications to seamlessly use AWS Cloud storage?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Backup", "B. Amazon Connect", "C. AWS Direct Connect", "CORRECT:D. AWS Storage Gateway"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/storagegateway/?whats-new-cards.sort-by=item.additionalFields.postDateTime&whats-new-cards.sort-order=desc","discussions": "3"}, "Question #187 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following acts as a virtual firewall at the Amazon EC2 instance level to control traffic for one or more instances?", "answers":[ "A. Access keys", "B. Virtual private gateways", "CORRECT:C. Security groups", "D. Access Control Lists (ACL)"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/ec2-security-groups.html","discussions": "2"}, "Question #188 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is the most efficient way to establish network connectivity from on-premises to multiple VPCs in different AWS Regions?", "answers":[ "A. Use AWS Direct Connect", "B. Use AWS VPN", "C. Use AWS Client VPN", "CORRECT:D. Use an AWS Transit Gateway"],"explanation": "Reference - https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/building-a-scalable-and-secure-multi-vpc-aws-network-infrastructure.pdf (11)","discussions": "3"}, "Question #189 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS Support plan provides access to architectural and operational reviews, as well as 24/7 access to Senior Cloud Support Engineers through email, online chat, and phone?", "answers":[ "A. Basic", "B. Business", "C. Developer", "CORRECT:D. Enterprise"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/enterprise/","discussions": "0"}, "Question #190 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service or feature helps restrict the AWS services, resources, and individual API actions the users and roles in each member account can access?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Cognito", "CORRECT:B. AWS Organizations", "C. AWS Shield", "D. AWS Firewall Manager"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_introduction.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #191 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is the best resource for a user to find compliance-related information and reports about AWS?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Artifact", "B. AWS Marketplace", "C. Amazon Inspector", "D. AWS Support"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/faq/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #192 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which Amazon S3 storage class is optimized to provide access to data with lower resiliency requirements, but rapid access when needed such as duplicate backups?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon S3 Standard", "B. Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive", "C. Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access", "D. Amazon S3 Glacier"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/s3/storage-classes/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #193 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is an Availability Zone in AWS?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. One or more physical data centers", "B. A completely isolated geographic location", "C. One or more edge locations based around the world", "D. A data center location with a single source of power and networking"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #194 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services can be used as infrastructure automation tools? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS CloudFormation", "B. Amazon CloudFront", "C. AWS Batch", "CORRECT:D. AWS OpsWorks", "E. Amazon QuickSight"],"explanation": "Reference: https://blog.newrelic.com/engineering/best-cloud-infrastructure-automation-tools/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #195 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service enables users to create copies of resources across AWS Regions?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon ElastiCache", "CORRECT:B. AWS CloudFormation", "C. AWS CloudTrail", "D. AWS Systems Manager"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-cloudformation-stacksets-to-provision-resources-across-multiple-aws-accounts-and-regions/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #196 Topic 2":{ "question":"A user would like to encrypt data that is received, stored, and managed by AWS CloudTrail. Which AWS service will provide this capability?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Secrets Manager", "B. AWS Systems Manager", "CORRECT:C. AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)", "D. AWS Certificate Manager"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awscloudtrail/latest/userguide/data-protection.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #197 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS Cloud benefit eliminates the need for users to try estimating future infrastructure usage?", "answers":[ "A. Easy and fast deployment of applications in multiple Regions around the world", "B. Security of the AWS Cloud", "CORRECT:C. Elasticity of the AWS Cloud", "D. Lower variable costs due to massive economies of scale"],"explanation": "","discussions": "1"}, "Question #198 Topic 2":{ "question":"What credential components are required to gain programmatic access to an AWS account? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. An access key ID", "B. A primary key", "CORRECT:C. A secret access key", "D. A user ID", "E. A secondary key"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws-sec-cred-types.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #199 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are AWS compute services? (Select two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Lightsail", "B. AWS Systems Manager", "C. AWS CloudFormation", "CORRECT:D. AWS Batch", "E. Amazon Inspector"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/compute-services.html","discussions": "0"}, "Question #200 Topic 2":{ "question":"How can a company separate costs for network traffic, Amazon EC2, Amazon S3, and other AWS services by department?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Add department-specific tags to each resource", "B. Create a separate VPC for each department", "C. Create a separate AWS account for each department", "D. Use AWS Organizations"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/custom-tags.html#allocation-how","discussions": "6"}, "Question #201 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is a benefit of consolidated billing for AWS accounts?", "answers":[ "A. Access to AWS Personal Health Dashboard", "CORRECT:B. Combined usage volume discounts", "C. Improved account security", "D. Centralized AWS IAM"],"explanation": "Reference: https://jayendrapatil.com/aws-consolidated-billing/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #202 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service will allow a user to set custom cost and usage limits, and will alert when the thresholds are exceeded?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Organizations", "CORRECT:B. AWS Budgets", "C. Cost Explorer", "D. AWS Trusted Advisor"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/hands-on/control-your-costs-free-tier-budgets/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #203 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides the ability to detect inadvertent data leaks of personally identifiable information (PII) and user credential data?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon GuardDuty", "B. Amazon Inspector", "CORRECT:C. Amazon Macie", "D. AWS Shield"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/macie/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #204 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which tool can be used to monitor AWS service limits?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator", "CORRECT:B. AWS Trusted Advisor", "C. AWS Personal Health Dashboard", "D. AWS Cost and Usage report"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/mt/monitoring-service-limits-with-trusted-advisor-and-amazon-cloudwatch/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #205 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company has distributed its workload on both the AWS Cloud and some on-premises servers. What type of architecture is this?", "answers":[ "A. Virtual private network", "B. Virtual private cloud", "CORRECT:C. Hybrid cloud", "D. Private cloud"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #206 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following describes a security best practice that can be implemented using AWS IAM?", "answers":[ "A. Disable AWS Management Console access for all users", "B. Generate secret keys for every IAM user", "CORRECT:C. Grant permissions to users who are required to perform a given task only", "D. Store AWS credentials within Amazon EC2 instances"],"explanation": "Reference: https://cloudcheckr.com/cloud-security/top-5-iam-best-practices/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #207 Topic 2":{ "question":"What can be used to automate and manage secure, well-architected, multi-account AWS environments?", "answers":[ "A. AWS shared responsibility model", "CORRECT:B. AWS Control Tower", "C. AWS Security Hub", "D. AWS Well-Architected Tool"],"explanation": "Control Tower automates the process of setting up a new baseline multi-account AWS environment that is secure, well-architected, and ready to use. Control Tower incorporates the knowledge that AWS Professional Service has gained over the course of thousands of successful customer engagements. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-control-tower-set-up-govern-a-multi-account-aws-environment/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #208 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service or feature allows a user to easily scale connectivity among thousands of VPCs?", "answers":[ "A. VPC peering", "CORRECT:B. AWS Transit Gateway", "C. AWS Direct Connect", "D. AWS Global Accelerator"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/training-and-certification/explore-the-aws-transit-gateway-networking-and-scaling-digital-course/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #209 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company needs protection from expanded distributed denial of service (DDoS) attacks on its website and assistance from AWS experts during such events. Which AWS managed service will meet these requirements?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Shield Advanced", "B. AWS Firewall Manager", "C. AWS WAF", "D. Amazon GuardDuty"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/ddos-overview.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #210 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company's application has flexible start and end times. Which Amazon EC2 pricing model will be the MOST cost-effective?", "answers":[ "A. On-Demand Instances", "CORRECT:B. Spot Instances", "C. Reserved Instances", "D. Dedicated Hosts"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #211 Topic 2":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, what are the customer's responsibilities? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Physical and environmental security", "B. Physical network devices including firewalls", "C. Storage device decommissioning", "CORRECT:D. Security of data in transit", "CORRECT:E. Data integrity authentication"],"explanation": "","discussions": "5"}, "Question #212 Topic 2":{ "question":"A cloud practitioner has a data analysis workload that is infrequently executed and can be interrupted without harm. To optimize for cost, which Amazon EC2 purchasing option should be used?", "answers":[ "A. On-Demand Instances", "B. Reserved Instances", "CORRECT:C. Spot Instances", "D. Dedicated Hosts"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #213 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS container service will help a user install, operate, and scale the cluster management infrastructure?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Elastic Container Registry (Amazon ECR)", "B. AWS Elastic Beanstalk", "CORRECT:C. Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)", "D. Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"],"explanation": "","discussions": "2"}}}